( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
You two worked together pretty well today.
لقد تعاونتما معاً بشكل جيد جداً اليوم.
Can I take that to mean
هل يمكنني أن أفهم من ذلك أن
you can team up again next time?
هل يمكنكم التعاون مجدداً في المرة القادمة؟
There won't be a next time.
لن يكون هناك مرة أخرى.
Siyuan is saying that
يقول سيوان ذلك
there won't be another chance where they need to work together to save you.
لن تكون هناك فرصة أخرى يحتاجون فيها إلى العمل معًا لإنقاذك.
You won't be in danger again.
لن تكون في خطر مرة أخرى.
Is that something hard to understand?
هل هذا شيء يصعب فهمه؟
You're almost thirty
أنت على وشك بلوغ الثلاثين
and still can't tell who's good or bad around you.
وما زلت لا أستطيع التمييز بين من هو جيد ومن هو سيئ من حولي.
I'll go clean up.
سأذهب لأنظف المكان.
Deal with those people from earlier.
تعامل مع هؤلاء الأشخاص الذين تحدثنا عنهم سابقاً.
Do you know that Secretary Zhang betrayed us?
هل تعلم أن السكرتير تشانغ قد خاننا؟
She was probably following Xia Shang's orders
ربما كانت تنفذ أوامر شيا شانغ
and planning to go after you and your people.
ويخططون لملاحقتك أنت وقومك.
By the way, Siyuan,
بالمناسبة، سيوان،
I ran into another group earlier today.
صادفت مجموعة أخرى في وقت سابق من اليوم.
They were the ones who kidnapped me and brought me here.
هم من اختطفوني وأحضروني إلى هنا.
I'll look into this.
سأبحث في هذا الأمر.
It's getting late.
لقد تأخر الوقت.
I'll take you home first.
سأوصلك إلى المنزل أولاً.
No need to trouble you.
لا داعي لإزعاجك.
Take care of your own business first
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة أولاً
before you worry about others.
قبل أن تقلق بشأن الآخرين.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Siyuan,
سيوان،
you and Li Xiang, be careful.
أنت ولي شيانغ، كونا حذرين.
From now on, don't let go of my hand.
من الآن فصاعدًا، لا تترك يدي.
And don't act alone.
ولا تتصرف بمفردك.
Honestly, seeing you with Siyuan today
بصراحة، رؤيتك مع سيوان اليوم أمر رائع
made me really happy.
لقد أسعدني ذلك حقاً.
So I got greedy and thought
لذا طمعت وفكرت
since there was a first time,
منذ أن كانت هناك مرة أولى،
there'd be a next time too.
سيكون هناك وقت آخر أيضاً.
I wasn't trying to
لم أكن أحاول
force you and my brother to make up.
أجبرك أنت وأخي على التصالح.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Working with someone you dislike
العمل مع شخص لا تحبه
must feel awful.
لا بد أن يكون شعوراً فظيعاً.
And I know
وأنا أعلم
you compromised because of me.
لقد تنازلت بسببي.
I'll make it up to you.
سأعوضك عن ذلك.
How?
كيف؟
I've got it.
فهمت.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Don't go back to that apartment.
لا تعود إلى تلك الشقة.
Move in with me.
انتقل للعيش معي.
Bear with it.
تحمّل الأمر.
I still have some things to take care of.
لا يزال لدي بعض الأمور التي يجب عليّ الاهتمام بها.
Once I'm done,
بمجرد أن أنتهي،
I'll come home.
سأعود إلى المنزل.
You go back first.
عليك العودة أولاً.
But
لكن
I'll be home
سأكون في المنزل
before midnight
قبل منتصف الليل
to celebrate your birthday.
للاحتفال بعيد ميلادك.
This scent
هذه الرائحة
is strong at first,
يكون قوياً في البداية،
but the middle and base notes get softer.
لكن النغمات الوسطى والسفلى تصبح أكثر نعومة.
Is it for your girlfriend?
هل هو لصديقتك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
My girlfriend
صديقتي الحميمة
passes off as cool,
يُعتبر رائعاً،
but she's actually
لكنها في الواقع
very comforting to be around.
من المريح جداً التواجد حوله.
Being with her makes you feel happy.
التواجد معها يجعلك تشعر بالسعادة.
Today
اليوم
is the third birthday she's had
هذا هو عيد ميلادها الثالث
since we got together.
منذ أن التقينا.
Why didn't you close the door?
لماذا لم تغلق الباب؟
You're so late.
لقد تأخرت كثيراً.
I almost couldn't wait for you anymore.
لم أعد أطيق الانتظار أكثر من ذلك.
Let's go to the hospital.
هيا بنا إلى المستشفى.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
It's not past midnight yet, right?
لم تتجاوز الساعة منتصف الليل بعد، أليس كذلك؟
I want to make a wish.
أريد أن أتمنى أمنية.
I wish.
أتمنى.
I had never
لم يسبق لي أن فعلت ذلك
made a pact with you.
لقد عقدت معك اتفاقاً.
That way, the man I love
وبهذه الطريقة، الرجل الذي أحبه
wouldn't die because of me.
لن يموت بسببي.
No.
لا.
That one doesn't count.
هذا لا يُحتسب.
You should wish
ينبغي أن تتمنى
that Wu Siyuan were foolish enough
أن وو سييوان كانوا حمقى بما فيه الكفاية
to lose
أن يخسر
the love of his life forever. (Watch on www, kisskh, id or www, kisskh, la to support Admin)
حب حياته إلى الأبد. (شاهد على www.kisskh.id أو www.kisskh.la لدعم المشرف)
And when he meets Li Xiang again in the next life,
وعندما يلتقي لي شيانغ مرة أخرى في الحياة الأخرى،
he'll be the one who loves more painfully.
سيكون هو من يحب بألم أكبر.
"The love of his life."
"حب حياته".
I don't think I'm afraid of death anymore.
لا أعتقد أنني أخشى الموت بعد الآن.
Got it. I'm coming back now.
فهمت. سأعود الآن.
Something urgent came up.
طرأ أمر عاجل.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Finish your cake and head home.
أنهِ تناول الكعكة وانطلق إلى المنزل.
Nongyu is sick.
نونغيو مريض.
I need to check on her.
أحتاج إلى الاطمئنان عليها.
Just leave it. I'll clean up when I get back.
اتركه كما هو. سأنظفه عندما أعود.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
عيد ميلاد سعيد لك!
♪ Happy birthday to Li Xiang ♪
♪ عيد ميلاد سعيد للي شيانغ ♪
[Master Short Videos from Scratch] So competitive.
[إتقان الفيديوهات القصيرة من الصفر] منافسة شديدة.
It's not enough to have a personal account.
لا يكفي أن يكون لديك حساب شخصي.
I even have to start live streaming.
حتى أنني اضطررت للبدء بالبث المباشر.
Good.
جيد.
How did it go?
كيف سارت الأمور؟
Wu Nongyu was rescued by Mr. Wu.
تم إنقاذ وو نونغيو بواسطة السيد وو.
But the other squad went pretty smoothly.
لكن الفريق الآخر سارت الأمور بسلاسة تامة.
Three Ren went berserk and broke into a house.
ثلاثة من الرين أصيبوا بالجنون واقتحموا منزلاً.
It just so happened another Ren lived there.
من قبيل الصدفة، كان يعيش هناك شخص آخر يُدعى رين.
All four of them died in a fight after losing control.
مات الأربعة جميعاً في شجار بعد أن فقدوا السيطرة.
Li Xiang has been taken care of.
تم الاعتناء بلي شيانغ.
Mr. Wu probably won't live much longer either.
من المحتمل ألا يعيش السيد وو لفترة أطول أيضاً.
Keep a close eye on Wu Nongyu.
راقبوا وو نونغيو عن كثب.
Yes, Director Xia.
نعم، أيها المخرج شيا.
Good luck with your live stream.
أتمنى لك التوفيق في البث المباشر.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Sleep a bit more.
نم قليلاً أكثر.
Breakfast will be ready soon.
سيكون الفطور جاهزاً قريباً.
You don't have to do this anymore.
لم يعد عليك فعل هذا.
I'm happy
أنا سعيد
to take care of you.
لأعتني بك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I shouldn't have threatened you
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أهددك
into staying with me
ابقَ معي
like some kind of sacrifice
كنوع من التضحية
to make up for what Wu Siyuan owes me.
لتعويض ما يدين به لي وو سييوان.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I've been the one taking so much love from you.
لقد كنت أنا من أخذ الكثير من الحب منك.
So from now on,
لذا من الآن فصاعدًا،
you just need to be yourself.
كل ما عليك فعله هو أن تكون على طبيعتك.
I'll be the one loving you more.
سأكون أنا من يحبك أكثر.
Okay?
تمام؟
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Okay.
تمام.
Then I'm going to take it all.
إذن سآخذ كل شيء.
You might
قد
not be able to handle it.
عدم القدرة على التعامل مع الأمر.
♪ A ray of morning sun shines through the cafe curtains ♪
♪ شعاع من شمس الصباح يتسلل عبر ستائر المقهى ♪
♪ Your fingertips touch the fantasy on the rim of the cup ♪
♪ تلمس أطراف أصابعك الخيال على حافة الكوب ♪
♪ The swaying wind chime knocks away the time difference ♪
♪ رنين أجراس الرياح المتأرجحة يزيل فارق التوقيت ♪
It feels so good to back for more sleep.
من الرائع العودة للنوم أكثر.
I don't even want to get out of bed today.
لا أريد حتى أن أنهض من السرير اليوم.
♪ The next second might change everything ♪
♪ قد تُغير الثانية التالية كل شيء ♪
♪ Sway along with the music... ♪
♪ تمايل مع الموسيقى... ♪
As you wish.
كما تشاء.
♪ Off-key becomes a romantic beat... ♪
♪ يتحول اللحن النشاز إلى إيقاع رومانسي... ♪
What porridge?
أي نوع من العصيدة؟
♪ It's showtime... ♪
♪ حان وقت العرض... ♪
Plain porridge.
عصيدة سادة.
♪ Tonight... ♪
♪ الليلة... ♪
What do you want instead?
ماذا تريد بدلاً من ذلك؟
I want sashimi porridge.
أريد عصيدة الساشيمي.
Sashimi porridge?
عصيدة الساشيمي؟
♪ You remind me of a romance film... ♪
♪ أنتِ تُذكرينني بفيلم رومانسي... ♪
I want strawberries.
أريد فراولة.
♪ From sea to shore ♪
♪ من البحر إلى الشاطئ ♪
♪ A fate bound to fall ♪
♪ مصير محتوم ♪
♪ Into the light... ♪
♪ إلى النور... ♪
One more.
واحد آخر.
♪ Lost in a captivating opera ♪
♪ ضائع في أوبرا آسرة ♪
♪ Frozen within ♪
♪ متجمد في الداخل ♪
♪ A melody left by the universe ♪
♪ لحنٌ تركه الكون ♪
♪ In every time and space ♪
♪ في كل زمان ومكان ♪
♪ I will meet you again ♪
♪ سأراك مجدداً ♪
I want water.
أريد ماءً.
Water.
ماء.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Up.
أعلى.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Hold the water first.
أمسك الماء أولاً.
Hold it.
انتظر.
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
Yeah.
نعم.
This is the best water I've had all year.
هذا أفضل ماء شربته طوال العام.
Really?
حقًا؟
Now you've got me curious.
لقد أثرت فضولي الآن.
Who said.
من قال ذلك؟
I meant from your mouth?
أقصد من فمك؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
You guys talk.
تكلموا يا رفاق.
Your husband
زوجك
seems pretty good.
يبدو جيداً جداً.
Is that something the Wu Siyuan I knew would say?
هل هذا شيء سيقوله وو سييوان الذي أعرفه؟
Current version of Wu Siyuan
النسخة الحالية من وو سيوان
thinks you're right.
أعتقد أنك على حق.
Ren have the ability to love.
رين لديها القدرة على الحب.
They can become
يمكنهم أن يصبحوا
good fathers,
الآباء الصالحون،
good friends,
أصدقاء جيدون،
and good partners.
وشركاء جيدين.
Wait.
انتظر.
Say that again.
قل ذلك مرة أخرى.
I need to record
أحتاج إلى التسجيل
everything you just said.
كل ما قلته للتو.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
So now
والآن
you've really changed your mind about Ren,
لقد غيرت رأيك حقاً بشأن رين،
right?
يمين؟
Yes.
نعم.
I deeply regret what I've done.
أشعر بندم شديد على ما فعلت.
♪ You smell like something strange ♪
♪ رائحتك غريبة ♪
♪ Like wood ♪
♪ مثل الخشب ♪
♪ Like wine ♪
♪ مثل النبيذ ♪
♪ Like the fading rain ♪
♪ مثل المطر المتلاشي ♪
♪ It's not a problem I can fix ♪
♪ إنها ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها ♪
♪ Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy ♪
♪ ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بين يديك ♪